jccc.edu 2007-06-30

# JCCC::Web Site Privacy Policy

Johnson County Community College  
12345 College Blvd.  
Overland Park, KS 66210-1299  
913-469-8500   

| 

Web Site Privacy Policy 

**B. PRIVACY POLICY**

1\. COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION FROM SITE VISITORS

JCCC automatically collects and/or tracks (a) the home server domain names, e-mail addresses, type of client computer, and type of Web browser of visitors to JCCC's Web site, (b) the e-mail addresses of visitors that communicate with JCCC via e-mail, post messages to JCCC's bulletin boards, or post messages to JCCCs chat groups, (c) information knowingly provided by the visitor in online registration forms, and (d) user-specific information on what pages visitors access. 

JCCC places Internet cookies on visitors' hard drives. Internet cookies save the visitors' name, password, user-name, screen preferences, the pages of JCCC's Web site viewed by the visitor, and the advertisements viewed or clicked by the visitor. When the visitor revisits JCCC's Web site, JCCC will recognize the visitor by the Internet cookie and customize the visitor’s experience accordingly. Internet cookies are stored on the visitor’s hard drive and are not stored, in any form, by JCCC. Visitors may decline the Internet cookie by using the appropriate feature of their Web client software, if available. 

2\. USE OF PERSONAL DATA COLLECTED 

Personal data collected by JCCC will be used by JCCC for editorial and feedback purposes, for marketing and promotional purposes, for a statistical analysis of users' behavior, for product development, for content improvement, to inform advertisers as to how many visitors have seen or clicked on their advertisements, and to customize content and layout of JCCC's site. Data on visitors' home servers is aggregated for internal review and then discarded. Names, postal and e-mail addresses, and phone numbers collected may be added to JCCC's databases and used for future calls and mailings regarding site updates, new classes or services and upcoming events. 

3\. COLLECTION OF PERSONAL DATA FROM CHILDREN 

JCCC will not collect or post information from children under the age of sixteen (children) without their parents' or guardians' consent. JCCC does not provide any personally identifying information collected from children, regardless of its source, to any third party for any purpose whatsoever. No information collected from children is used for any marketing or promotional purposes whatsoever, either inside or outside JCCC. 

4\. JCCC'S RIGHT TO CONTACT USER 

JCCC reserves the right to contact site visitors regarding account status and changes to the subscriber agreement, privacy policy or any other policies or agreements relevant to site visitors. 

5\. JCCC'S RIGHT TO CHANGE PRIVACY POLICY 

JCCC reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying visitors of the existence and location of the new or revised privacy policy. 

### Information Privacy and Security
